

ABOUT EXPERIENCE EDUCATION SKILLS

INTERESTS

RECOMMENDATIONS



Graduated in July 2018 in Information Technologies at Faculdade de Ciencias da Universidade de Lisboa, After a rocky start in Colege, I've worked a lot and learned a lot in the last few years, and it started to grow on me, a passion with programming.

The constant challenge of solving problems and the enormous number of possibilities that programming gives, in order to solve them, gives me a sense of freedom, freedom of thinking.

Honestly, I don't know every single java function or pattern in the book (I google it), but I have the most important skill set, in my opinion, I know how to think, I know how to teach a machine to do what I want it to do.

I consider myself a proactive, Hard-working, Dynamic and Enthusiastic person, who contributes to a healthy and optimal working environment. My favorite coding language is PHP.



EXPERIENCE

July 2018 - Present **PROGRAMMER**

PCDIGA

Working mainly in the Company's BackOffice Platform, in PHP, using the MVC Framework Laravel, this platform is also integrated with SAP business one service layer API and the e-commerce platform Magento.

Our main goal with this platform is to optimize other employees functionalities, in order to make their jobs easier, giving them the best UX and UI possible.

February 2016 - April 2016 SALESMAN

WIME

This position came when at the end of The CR7 Travelling Museum project, the CEO invited me to another project of his, this one related to Wine.

STORE ACCOUNTABLE / GRAPHIC DESIGNER / MULTIMEDIA CONTENT CR7 TRAVELLING MUSEUM

Initially, I started as a salesman in the Museum Store in the Vilamoura Edition, as the time went by, I grew inside the company and took over more responsibilities regarding managing and even decision making. In the late stages of the project, the museum traveled to Dubai, where I worked for about 2 months, where I was responsible for the setup and

Some footage of the artwork.

the graphic artwork of the store and museum.

EDUCATION

FACULDADE DE CIENCIAS DA UNIVERSIDADE DE LISBOA

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Information Technologies GPA: 15

ESCOLA SECUNDÁRIA JOSÉ GOMES FERREIRA

SCIENCE PROGRAM

August 2011 - May 2014, August 2016 - July 2018

August 2008 - May 2011

July 2015 - Ferbruary 2016

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & TOOLS

Ordered by experience





























MAIN PROJECTS

- ✓ Poker, Texas Hold'em Online, Aplications and Web Services, Grade: 18
- ✓ Checkers Game, Inteligent Systems, Grade: 16 ✓ Management and control of FCUL accesses, Final Project, Grade:
- ✓ Sales System, Software Systems Construction, Grade: 20

INTERESTS

Apart from being an IT student, I have a healthy lifestyle, besides my coffe addiction;), I enjoy most of my time being outdoors, hanging out with friends, play football, basketball, going to the gym.

When forced indoors, I follow a lot of television shows, I play a lot of online games with friends and I love to cook, some say I am an aspiring chef.

RECOMMENDATIONS

Recommendation Letter, Pedro Sá, CR7 Travelling Museum Manager



CERTIDÃO DE CONCLUSÃO

Maria Fernanda Adão dos Santos Fernandes de Oliveira, Subdiretora da Faculdade de Ciências da Universidade de Lisboa, certifica que João Miguel Dias Amado, de nacionalidade portuguesa, nascido a 20 de outubro de 1993, portador do Cartão de Cidadão n.º 14374289, obteve aprovação nas seguintes unidades curriculares da Licenciatura em Tecnologias de Informação - Minor em Design Multimédia, que concluiu a 6 de julho de 2018, com a classificação final de 15 (Quinze) valores e a classe B na Escala Europeia de Comparabilidade de Classificações (EECC), tendo direito ao Grau Académico de Licenciado:

Unidades Curriculares	Data Aprovação	Nota ^t	ECTS ²	EECC,
26745 - Programação I (LTIC)	2012-01-10	13	6.0	32(5)/63
93102 - Informática na Ótica do Utilizador	2012-01-13	AP	3.0	
13501 - Elementos de Matemática Discreta	2012-01-17	10	6.0	D
93101 - Inglês a)	2012-01-30	AP	3.0	0000
26702 - Arquiteturas de Computadores	2012-01-31	15	6.0	A
22701 - Introdução às Probabilidades e Estatística	2012-06-04	14	6.0	В
85104 - História dos Jogos de Tabuleiro	2012-07-03	15	3.0	D
26710 - Fundamentos e Técnicas de Visualização	2013-01-14	12	6.0	С
26708 - Interação com Computadores	2013-01-28	13	6.0	C
26743 - Sistemas Operativos (LTIC)	2013-06-12	12	6.0	С
26744 - Redes de Computadores (LTIC)	2013-06-15	16	6.0	A
26706 - Programação Centrada em Objetos	2014-01-20	14	6.0	21(4)/49
26707 - Bases de Dados	2014-01-21	14	6.0	В
26760 - Processamento de Dados	2017-01-05	16	3.0	В
26737 - Teoria da Computação	2017-01-17	14	6.0	C
26711 - Análise e Desenho de Software	2017-06-08	19	6.0	A
26752 - Sistemas Inteligentes	2017-06-14	14	6.0	C
26757 - Programação II (LTI)	2017-06-16	15	6.0	C
26709 - Aplicações Distribuídas	2017-06-17	15	6.0	C

26712 - Aplicações e Serviços na Web	2017-06-19	15	6.0	C
26751 - Introdução às Tecnologias Web	2017-06-20	14	6.0	C
26713 - Conceção de Produto	2017-07-06	15	6.0	С
26758 - Construção de Sistemas de Software (LTI)	2018-01-05	17	6.0	A
10043 - Webdesign II	2018-01-16	15	6.0	C
10047 - Audiovisual e Multimédia I	2018-01-16	16	6.0	A
10051 - Marketing	2018-01-16	16	3.0	В
26716 - Planeamento e Gestão de Projeto	2018-02-01	15	6.0	В
10048 - Audiovisual e Multimédia II	2018-06-14	15	6.0	С
10042 - Webdesign I	2018-06-18	18	6.0	Α
26718 - Projeto de Tecnologias de Redes	2018-06-29	17	6.0	В
26719 - Projeto de Tecnologias de Informação	2018-06-29	17	6.0	В
13566 - Elementos de Matemática II	2018-07-03	13	6.0	В
10041 - Design de Informação	2018-07-06	15	3.0	С

a) Creditação

A presente certidão vai firmada com o selo branco da Faculdade de Ciências da Universidade de Lisboa.

O aluno já requereu a certidão de registo do grau.

Faculdade de Ciências da Universidade de Lisboa, em 2 de agosto de 2018

Fernanda Oliveira

A Subdiretora

Nota

(0-20 (escala); AP - Aprovado)

A - Aprovado

ECTS - Sistema Europeu de Transferência e Acumulação de Créditos

EECC - Escala Europeia de Comparabilidade de Classificações

(A - Excelente; B - Muito Bom; C - Bom; D - Satisfaz; E - Suficiente)

Emolumento: 20,00 €

Emitido por

Conferido por



Alfragide, 3 de Março de 2016

Carta de recomendação

A quem possa interessar,

Tive o prazer de trabalhar durante vários meses com o João Miguel Dias Amado, portador do CC nº 14374289, e é com muito gosto que o recomendo pelo desempenho demonstrado durante a sua contribuição para a Buy Gift, onde provou ser um ativo valioso.

O seu trabalho incluía, entre outras atividades, a gestão e supervisão de uma loja de retalho, especificamente a loja do Museu itinerante Cristiano Ronaldo, a qual era operada pela Buy Gift. No entanto, ao longo da sua colaboração com a nossa empresa o João acabou por abraçar um vasto leque de responsabilidades, nomeadamente ao nível da gestão do próprio Museu, do design gráfico e da edição multimédia. Enquanto trabalhou connosco, provou ser um colaborador competente, com iniciativa e brio profissional, e gostaria de sublinhar que o João foi um dos melhores recursos da vasta equipa que acompanhou várias edições do Museu itinerante Cristiano Ronaldo.

Tenho o gosto de dizer que ele é um verdadeiro companheiro de equipa, uma pessoa agradável e sincera, e um colega leal. Estou satisfeito por ter tido a oportunidade de trabalhar com ele, o João sempre criou um bom espírito de equipa e todos gostavam dele.

Posso recomendar o João fortemente para qualquer trabalho que requeira a sua responsabilidade. Ele é o tipo de pessoas com quem toda a gente gosta de trabalhar.

Sem mais de momento, subscrevo-me com os meus melhores cumprimentos,

Pedro Sá Diretor Geral